[
  {
    "level": "3",
    "question": "ADD R4,R5,1",
    "options": ["1- True", "2- False"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "3",
    "question": "MOV R1,10",
    "options": ["1- True", "2- False"],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "3",
    "question": "XORR SR ",
    "options": ["1- True", "2- False"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "3",
    "question": "NOT 20*",
    "options": ["1- True", "2- False"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "3",
    "question": "NAND BR, SR",
    "options": ["1- True", "2- False"],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "3",
    "question": "SUB RI ,20",
    "options": ["1- True", "2- False"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "3",
    "question": "MOV R2,BR*+10",
    "options": ["1- True", "2- False"],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "3",
    "question": "NAND BR, SR",
    "options": ["1- True", "2- False"],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "3",
    "question": "XOR IR",
    "options": ["1- True", "2- False"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "3",
    "question": "XOR R1,5",
    "options": ["1- True", "2- False"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  }
]
